NICK JAY BAGUIO

+63 912 6675 199

0629575098

b.nickjay05@gmail.com

Malangas, Zamboanga Sibugay, Philippines



FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE INFO

I am a Full Time Full Stack Developer with more than 4+ years of comprehensive experience in Developing Web Applications. Certified in both Front-end and Back-end technologies. I am a Web Programmer by profession. I am one of the few people in this world that truly gets to do what they love. I am self taught, but have built my skills to be able to work with some really amazing clients

SKILLS

SPECIALITIES

Full-Stack Web Development

PHP, Codelgniter, Laravel

ReactJS, VueJS

jQuery, Bootstrap

9 NI/NX

TOOLS

IIS, XAMPP, NGIX

Visual Studio Code

Figma

Photoshop

EDUCATION

MALANGAS CENTRAL ELEMENTARY, SCHOOL PRIMARY 2003-2009

MALANGAS INSTITUTE SECONDARY 2009-2013

WESTERN MINDANAO STATE UNIVERSITY ASSOCIATE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE 2013-2015

WESTERN MINDANAD STATE UNIVERSITY BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE 2015-2017

WORK EXPERIENCE

STUDENT ASSISTANT (SA)

Arcer Computer Educational Development System

• FROM 2012 - 2013

I've been part of the team that teaches other students and school teachers in IT Related Course, Like: Word Processing, Spreadsheets, Vector Graphics, Photoshop and some basic concepts of programming

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES

 Assist and guide the students with the modules used in every session provider by head instructor.

GAME DEVELOPER/FULL STACK DEVELOPER

TANTRA ETERNAL

• FROM 2017 - 2018

I run a Private MMORPG Game called Tantra, Though server files of the game is not mine, But my skills on handling game servers have been enhanced (e.g. networking, security, game strategy, game website).

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES

- \bullet Fulltime Game Admin, i'd monitor all the events inside the game.
- Website Developer, i'd develop a website for the game, which users
 can sign in and sign up, they can check the ranks, events, taneys and
 buy items.
- Maintain the Server, i am the one who fix the bugs and issues occur inside the server.
- Doing updates and improvements

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

198 Internet Services

• FROM 2018 - 2019

We do eCommerce Stores with advance eCommerce Admin Features and other medium and small scale web projects.

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES

- Full Stack Developer (Front-end, Back-end)
- Develop Web Projects includes eCommerce, Landing Pages, etc.

REFERENCE

YURI GERMAN CEO, 198 Internet Services +97 254 304 6162

MA, CELESTE B. DELA CRUZ Faculty Head, WMSU Malangas +63 916 118 8504

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

FREELANCE

• FROM 2018 - PRESENT

I'am now currently working as freelance fullstack web developer, doing business with remote clients, help them to build thier desired web applications.

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES

- I develop any types of websites (eCommerce, Shop, Hotel, Management, Portfolio, Travel & Tours, Blog, Real State)
- Implement back-end and front-end technologies
- Maximized applications' efficiency, data quality, scope, operability, and flexibility.
- Managed, optimized, and updated PHP databases as necessary.
- Developed app integration with REST and other APIs for Google Maps, social media logins, payment processors, and other services.

VISITING LECTURER (VL)

WESTERN MINDANAO STATE UNIVERSITY(WMSU)

• FROM 2019 - PRESENT

I am currently a part time lecturer in college, i teach computer programming course.

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES

• Instruct the students and teach computer programming